[
	{
		"question": "What does the Trivia Bot want to do?",
		"answers": ["Create interesting content", "Teach Minecraft trivia", "Get on the Nice List!"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What enchantment do you need to walk over powdered snow?",
		"answers": ["Depth Strider", "Frost Walker", "Feather Falling", "None of these are correct"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What would win, 100 Strays or 1 Warden?",
		"answers": ["1 Warden", "One of each Pokemon", "100 Strays"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Is \"Nightmare Before Christmas\" a Halloween movie or a Christmas movie?",
		"answers": ["Both", "A Christmas movie", "A Halloween movie"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What came first?",
		"answers": ["The Chicken", "The Egg", "We'll never know"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which Life Series season ran closest to the holidays?",
		"answers": ["Double Life", "Secret Life", "Limited Life", "Wild Life"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What dates are chests retextured into presents in Minecraft?",
		"answers": ["December 25", "December 24 to 26", "December 12-31"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these items cannot be used on an already existing Snow Golem?",
		"answers": ["Lead", "Shears", "Carved Pumpkin", "Name Tag"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Is it possible for a carved pumpkin to naturally spawn?",
		"answers": ["Yes, in vanilla world generation", "No, never", "Only with custom generation rules"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Is it possible to spawn a Snow Golem by placing the blocks sideways?",
		"answers": ["Yes", "No"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "I could be a bird, the sand, or the sun. What am I?",
		"answers": ["A person", "A clock", "A pond", "A phoenix"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "According to the Life Series players, which player was voted naughtiest?",
		"answers": ["Joel", "Scar", "Martyn", "Timmy"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Is it possible to spawn a Snow Golem by placing the blocks upside down?",
		"answers": ["Yes", "No"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these Life Series team's base exteriors was built almost entirely out of snow?",
		"answers": ["Birthday Cake", "Heart Foundation", "Shadow Alliance", "Team B.E.S.T.", "The Villies"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	}
]